<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on </title>
    <link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Set Up</title>
      <link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Beta Notice GlimBoi is in beta. There will be bugs and other issues. I will issue patches for any issues found as quickly as possible.
Please be patient :)
Download Releases Page
Start by downloading the installation file for your plaltform (.exe for windows and .deb for linux). Windows users can run the .exe file and choose where the bot will be installed. Linux users will need a package manager that can extract .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commands</title>
      <link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/commands/</guid>
      <description>Basic Info Commands work the same as any other chatbot. A viewer types !commandName in chat and a script is ran. This script is divided into &amp;ldquo;actions&amp;rdquo;. Actions are instructions for the command. Commands are created on the commands page or from chat using the syntax -
 !command add !NAME RESPONSE !command new !NAME RESPONSE !cmd add !NAME RESPONSE !cmd new !NAME RESPONSE !cmd remove !NAME * Not yet Public, delete from the GUI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Users</title>
      <link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>User Controls GlimBoi must add a viewer as a user to store data on them. You can do this manually or let the bot automatically detect new users (ran every 15 minutes. Users can be added and removed at any time.
Adding Users You can add users from the users page. You can also add them by typing the following in chat (permissions dependent) -
 !user new NAME !user add NAME  Removing Users You can remove users from the users page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/events/</guid>
      <description>Events Overview Glimboi can start various events. Events can be joined by viewers in chat. Multiple events can run at the same time.
Raffle Glimboi can start a raffle. The bot will pick one winner. A raffle can be started on the events page or by typing !raffle in chat. Viewers can enter the raffle with !enter . You can view the list of participants on the events page. It will live update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overlay</title>
      <link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/overlay/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/overlay/</guid>
      <description>Overlay Overview The Glimboi overlay will react to certain events in the bot. You need to add the overlay as a browser source in OBS. Once added the media will show up on your stream. The overlay file is located on the modal prompt &amp;ldquo;Launch Overlay&amp;rdquo;.
Adding Media Before you can add sound effects and displayable media you need to add the media to the database. Go to the overlay page and add a few items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Currency System</title>
      <link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/points/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/points/</guid>
      <description>Currency Overview Viewers can become users in GlimBoi. Once they are added as a user they can start to earn currency. Every 15 minutes the bot will check if the user has spoken in chat. If the user has been active Glimboi will give the user a set amount of points. These points can be used for features within the bot.
Chat Commands (Info):
 !points : Returns how many points the user has.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Settings</title>
      <link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/settings/</guid>
      <description>Settings Overview Glimboi has a few settings to help you customize the bot for your stream.
Chat Health Reminder If enabled Glimboi will remind you to stretch, drink water, and take a break if neccassary. You can set the interval or turn it off completly.
Log Messages If enabled Glimboi will log every chat message to a text file. When you join a chat Glimboi will ask you which file you want to save the log to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
