<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on</title><link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Set Up</title><link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/introduction/</guid><description>Beta Notice The bot will be ready for download before Glimesh launches. You can explore the features on this website to get an idea of what the bot will have for launch.
When a download is ready I will delete this message and link it in the below tutorial.
GlimBoi will be in beta. There will be bugs and other issues. I will issue patches for any issues found as quickly as possible.</description></item><item><title>Commands</title><link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/commands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/commands/</guid><description>Basic Info Commands work the same as any other chatbot. A viewer types !commandName in chat and a response is sent. Commands are created on the commands page or from chat using the syntax -
!command add !NAME RESPONSE !command new !NAME RESPONSE !cmd add !NAME RESPONSE !cmd new !NAME RESPONSE !cmd remove !NAME * Not yet Public, delete from the GUI. * !cmd del !NAME * Not yet public, delete from the GUI * Arguments This feature is currently unimplemented.</description></item><item><title>Users</title><link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/quick-start/</guid><description>User Controls GlimBoi must add a viewer as a user to store data on them. This helps the bot to save disk space and resources. Users can be added and removed at any time.
Adding Users You can add users from the users page. You can also add them by typing the following in chat -
!user new NAME !user add NAME Removing Users You can remove users from the users page.</description></item><item><title>Events</title><link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/events/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/events/</guid><description>Events Overview Glimboi can start various events. Events can be joined by viewers in chat. Multiple events can run at the same time. Currently the only supported event is the raffle. Bankheist, polls, trivia, and more are coming soon!
Raffle Glimboi can start a raffle. The bot will pick one winner. A raffle can be started on the events page or by typing !raffle in chat. Viewers can enter the raffle with !</description></item><item><title>Currency System</title><link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/points/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/points/</guid><description>Currency Overview Viewers can become users in GlimBoi. Once they are added as a user they can start to earn currency. Every 15 minutes the bot will check if the user has spoken in chat. If the user has been active Glimboi will give the user a set amount of points. These points can be used for features within the bot.
Currency Settings You can change the amount of points that a user starts with.</description></item><item><title>Settings</title><link>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/settings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://aMytho.github.io/GlimBoi/docs/intro/settings/</guid><description>Settings Overview Glimboi has a few settings to help you customize the bot for your stream.
Cooldown Glimboi will apply a cooldown to all commands. This prevents viewers from spamming the chat with commands. This applies to ALL commands, not just one command being repeated. Below is an example of how this might work.
30 second cooldown -
!info - Sent to chat
5 seconds later !other - Not sent to chat</description></item></channel></rss>